<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Cereva</string>
    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string-array name="reminder_messages">
        <item>"Today, you see a child laughing with delight. The sound is contagious, and you find yourself smiling too. Take a moment to appreciate the simple joy around you."</item>
        <item>
            "Imagine a stranger holding the door open for you with a warm smile. You thank them, and they nod kindly. Feel the warmth of that small gesture brighten your day."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You notice a beautiful flower blooming in an unexpected place. Take a deep breath and let its colors and fragrance lift your spirits."
        </item>
        <item>
             "Picture yourself in line at a coffee shop. The person behind you compliments your outfit. You thank them, and it feels like a shared moment of kindness."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine getting an unexpected call or message from a friend, simply to say hello. Feel the joy of being remembered and cherished."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You hold the door open for someone, and they give you a heartfelt 'Thank you!' Appreciate the small kindness you offered and received."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Today, while walking, you notice a bird singing cheerfully. Pause, listen, and let its melody brighten your mood."
        </item>
        <item>
             "Visualize yourself helping someone who looks lost by offering directions. Their gratitude makes you feel light and happy."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine finding a beautifully written quote in a book. It speaks to you deeply, inspiring joy and reflection."
        </item>
        <item>
             "You see someone picking up litter and throwing it away. Feel gratitude for the goodness in people’s hearts."
        </item>

        <item>
             "Today, when you step outside, you meet a friendly stranger. You exchange warm smiles. You compliment their hairstyle, 'Your hair looks great today!' They thank you, beaming. Visualize this joyful connection brightening your day"
        </item>

        <item>
            "Today, you see a child laughing with delight. The sound is contagious, and you find yourself smiling too. Take a moment to appreciate the simple joy around you."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine a stranger holding the door open for you with a warm smile. You thank them, and they nod kindly. Feel the warmth of that small gesture brighten your day."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You notice a beautiful flower blooming in an unexpected place. Take a deep breath and let its colors and fragrance lift your spirits."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Picture yourself in line at a coffee shop. The person behind you compliments your outfit. You thank them, and it feels like a shared moment of kindness."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine getting an unexpected call or message from a friend, simply to say hello. Feel the joy of being remembered and cherished."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You hold the door open for someone, and they give you a heartfelt 'Thank you!' Appreciate the small kindness you offered and received."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Today, while walking, you notice a bird singing cheerfully. Pause, listen, and let its melody brighten your mood."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Visualize yourself helping someone who looks lost by offering directions. Their gratitude makes you feel light and happy"
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine finding a beautifully written quote in a book. It speaks to you deeply, inspiring joy and reflection."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You see someone picking up litter and throwing it away. Feel gratitude for the goodness in people’s hearts."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine receiving a random compliment from a stranger. Let it remind you of the beauty others see in you."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Picture yourself smiling at someone and watching as their face lights up. Embrace the shared happiness."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You see a vibrant rainbow after a rain shower. Marvel at the colors and let them fill you with hope."
        </item><item>
            "Imagine finding a cozy spot in a park where you can relax and enjoy nature. Feel the peace settling within you."
        </item>
        <item>
            "A barista writes a happy face on your coffee cup. Appreciate this small act and let it make you smile."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You come across a friendly dog wagging its tail. Take a moment to enjoy its pure happiness and feel your spirits lift."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine receiving a kind email or message from a coworker thanking you. Let it remind you of the value you bring to others."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Picture yourself complimenting someone on their positive energy. They thank you sincerely, and you feel the warmth of their gratitude."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Today, while walking, you feel the sun on your skin. Appreciate its warmth and let it bring you peace."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You see a stranger picking up something you dropped. Feel grateful for their kindness and the small moments of connection."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine discovering a new song that makes you feel alive and joyful. Let the music fill you with energy"
        </item>
        <item>
            ""
        </item><item>
            "A child waves at you from across the street. Wave back and appreciate the sweet simplicity of human connection."
        </item><item>
            "Picture someone helping you carry something heavy. Feel the relief and appreciation for their support"
        </item>
        <item>
            "You share a genuine laugh with someone you just met. Let the warmth of laughter fill your heart"
        </item>

        <item>
            "Imagine meeting an old friend and feeling instantly at ease. Embrace the joy of reconnecting with someone special."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Picture a stranger complimenting your smile. Let their words remind you of the beauty you bring into the world."
        </item>


        <item>
"You find a perfect place to watch the sunset. Relax and let the colors of the sky fill you with wonder."
        </item>


        <item>
"Imagine receiving a handwritten note from a loved one. Cherish the care and thoughtfulness behind each word."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Picture yourself helping someone in a small way, like sharing an umbrella. Feel the warmth of kindness."

        </item>


        <item>
 "You hear someone singing softly, lost in their own world. Let their joy remind you to embrace simple pleasures."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Imagine being surrounded by flowers, each with a different color and fragrance. Let their beauty fill you with peace."
        </item>


        <item>
"Picture yourself being surprised with a warm hug from a friend. Feel the comfort and connection in that embrace."
        </item>


        <item>
"You receive a compliment on something you worked hard on. Let it remind you that your efforts are seen and appreciated."

        </item>


        <item>
 "Imagine feeling a cool breeze on a warm day. Breathe it in and let it refresh and invigorate you."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Picture finding a handwritten message of encouragement left for someone else. Feel inspired to spread kindness."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Today, you notice a beautiful cloud formation in the sky. Pause and enjoy the quiet beauty above you."

        </item>


        <item>
 "You hear someone share good news about their life. Share in their joy and let it uplift your own spirit."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Imagine yourself complimenting someone’s laugh. Their happiness fills you with warmth and light."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Picture a stranger sharing a knowing smile with you over a funny situation. Enjoy this silent connection."

        </item>


        <item>
 "You find a hidden garden full of colorful flowers. Let the tranquility of the space wash over you."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Imagine seeing a couple sharing a warm moment together. Appreciate the love and connection in the world."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Today, you find a quote that resonates with you deeply. Let its wisdom stay with you and bring you peace."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Picture receiving a kind gesture from a stranger, like someone letting you go ahead in line. Appreciate the small act."
        </item>


        <item>
 "Imagine seeing someone dance happily on their own. Let their joy remind you of the beauty in spontaneity."
        </item>


        <item>
  "You help someone in a small way, like holding a door open. Let the gratitude in their smile brighten your day."
        </item>

        <item>
 "Imagine coming across an inspiring artwork that moves you. Let it remind you of the creativity within each of us."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture finding a quiet spot to enjoy your favorite drink. Relish in the peace of the moment just for you."
        </item>
        <item>
"Today, a friendly barista smiles and remembers your name. Feel the warmth of being noticed and remembered."
        </item>
        <item>
"You receive a compliment on something unique about you. Let it remind you to appreciate your individuality."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine hearing a beautiful piece of music that resonates deeply. Let it uplift and inspire you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture sharing a smile with a stranger as you pass each other. Feel the joy of a momentary connection."
        </item>
        <item>
  "You see an elderly couple holding hands. Let their lifelong love and connection warm your heart."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine finding a quote in a book that speaks to you. Let its wisdom bring clarity and peace to your thoughts."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Today, someone says thank you for a small gesture. Let their appreciation remind you of the impact of kindness."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture yourself taking a walk surrounded by trees and nature. Let the beauty of the world soothe your soul."
        </item>
        <item>
 "You hear laughter from a nearby group of friends. Share in their joy and feel connected to the happiness around you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine helping someone cross the street safely. Their gratitude reminds you of the value in helping others."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture receiving a simple 'Good morning' greeting from a neighbor. Feel the warmth of community."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Today, you hear a beautiful story from a stranger. Feel grateful for the connections we can find in every interaction."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine someone thanking you for a piece of advice you gave. Their appreciation fills you with purpose."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture discovering a quiet, beautiful spot you've never noticed before. Let the peace of the place settle within you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Today, you find a beautiful feather on the ground. Appreciate its lightness and delicate beauty."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine a stranger offering to help you with something. Feel the comfort of shared humanity."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture someone giving you a genuine compliment. Let it remind you that you are valued and seen."
        </item>
        <item>
 "You see a child giving their parent a big hug. Enjoy the warmth of witnessing such pure love."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine a close friend saying they appreciate having you in their life. Let their words fill you with gratitude."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Today, you see a butterfly fluttering past. Pause and marvel at its beauty and grace."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture someone noticing you’ve had a hard day and offering support. Feel the comfort of their understanding."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine receiving a compliment on your kindness. Let it remind you of the positive impact you have on others."
        </item>
        <item>
 "You see someone comforting a friend. Feel inspired by the power of compassion and connection."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine helping someone by sharing a small piece of advice. Their gratitude fills you with a sense of purpose."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a stranger giving you a friendly nod or wave. Enjoy this small but meaningful connection."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Today, you find a stone with a beautiful pattern. Admire its uniqueness and let it ground you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine someone appreciating your sense of humor. Let their laughter remind you of the joy you bring to others."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture witnessing someone being kind to an animal. Feel inspired by their gentleness and care."
        </item>
        <item>
"You see two friends taking a joyful photo together. Appreciate the shared happiness of those around you."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine discovering a handwritten note of kindness left for a stranger. Let it remind you of the good in the world."
        </item>
        <item>
"Today, you see a child playing with a pet, full of laughter. Enjoy their innocent joy and let it uplift you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a loved one saying they’re grateful for you. Let their words fill you with warmth and love."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine seeing a beautiful sunrise. Let the light of a new day bring hope and positivity."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture someone sharing a beautiful memory with you. Feel honored by their openness."
        </item>
        <item>
             "Today, you see a couple dancing together in the street. Share in their joy and let it bring a smile to your face."
        </item>
        <item>
             "Imagine a stranger helping someone pick up something they dropped. Appreciate the kindness in others."
        </item>
        <item>
  "You find a cozy spot to read or relax. Enjoy the tranquility and take a deep breath."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture someone giving you an unexpected compliment on your personality. Let it brighten your day."
        </item>
        <item>
"Today, you share a heartfelt conversation with a friend. Feel grateful for the depth of your connection."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine hearing a song that brings back happy memories. Let it remind you of beautiful moments in your life."
        </item>
        <item>
 "You find a little note from a friend saying how much they appreciate you. Let it fill you with joy and gratitude."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a kind stranger offering to help with something small. Feel grateful for their consideration."
        </item>
        <item>
"Today, you witness a stranger giving a flower to someone. Appreciate the beauty of simple gestures."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine hearing laughter from a loved one. Let their happiness fill you with warmth and peace."
        </item>
        <item>
"You meet a new friend who shares similar interests. Appreciate the joy of finding a kindred spirit."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Picture someone noticing something unique about you and complimenting it. Feel valued and seen."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Today, you receive unexpected praise for something you did. Let it fill you with pride and confidence."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine discovering a quiet place where you feel at ease. Enjoy the peace it brings."
        </item>
        <item>
            "You see a child and their pet playing with pure joy. Let it remind you of the beauty in simple happiness."
        </item>
        <item>
             "Picture a loved one saying they’re proud of you. Let their words lift your spirits."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine someone telling you that you made their day better. Feel the warmth of knowing you made a difference."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Today, you find yourself inspired by a small act of kindness. Let it encourage you to share more kindness in the world."
        </item>
        <item>
 "You find a comforting message in a book. Let its words stay with you and bring you peace."
        </item>
        <item>
            "Imagine the most beautiful sunset you've ever seen. Picture yourself there, feeling the warmth of the colors and the peace filling your heart."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Recall the softest blanket you've ever wrapped yourself in. Now imagine snuggling up in it, feeling its warmth and comfort all around you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of the sound of rain gently tapping on a window. Picture yourself listening to it, feeling cozy and peaceful, as if the whole world is at rest."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember the smell of freshly baked bread. Imagine breathing it in deeply, savoring the comforting warmth and richness in the air."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture a place where you felt completely at peace. Imagine standing there now, surrounded by that same calmness and beauty."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall the laughter of a close friend. Imagine hearing it again, letting the joy and warmth of that moment fill your heart."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of a moment when you were surrounded by nature, like a forest or a beach. Picture yourself there, feeling connected and alive."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember the best compliment you ever received. Imagine hearing it again and let that feeling of appreciation fill you with warmth."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Picture a sunny day with a gentle breeze. Imagine yourself there, feeling the sun on your skin and the wind gently caressing your face."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a time you felt incredibly proud of yourself. Imagine feeling that pride again, letting it fill you with confidence."
        </item>
        <item>
"Think of a moment when someone showed you unexpected kindness. Picture it, feeling grateful and inspired to pass it on."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember the taste of a sweet fruit, perfectly ripe. Imagine biting into it again, savoring its sweetness and freshness."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture yourself walking barefoot on warm sand. Feel each grain between your toes and the gentle warmth grounding you."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine standing on a mountaintop, looking at a beautiful view. Breathe in the fresh air and let the vastness fill you with awe."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a time you danced with joy. Imagine dancing again, feeling free, light, and joyful as if nothing else matters."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of the soft glow of a candle in a dim room. Picture it now, feeling calm as the warm light fills the space."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember a moment when someone you love hugged you tightly. Imagine that embrace, feeling safe, loved, and connected."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture yourself lying in a field of flowers. Breathe in their fragrance, feeling surrounded by beauty and peace."
        </item>
        <item>
"Think of the sound of waves gently crashing on the shore. Imagine sitting there, letting the rhythm soothe your soul."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a time you laughed uncontrollably. Picture yourself laughing again, feeling light, happy, and carefree."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine a cool drink on a hot day. Feel its refreshing chill as it cools you from the inside out."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture yourself in a cozy cabin during a snowfall. Look out the window, feeling warm, peaceful, and safe inside."
        </item>
        <item>
"Think of a time you felt truly understood. Imagine that feeling again, feeling seen, heard, and valued."
        </item>
        <item>
"Recall a moment you accomplished something big. Imagine the pride and excitement filling you up again."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a beautiful butterfly landing near you. Watch it closely, marveling at its delicate colors and graceful movements."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine standing under a clear, star-filled sky. Feel the wonder and awe as you look up, connected to the vast universe."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Remember the smell of fresh coffee or tea in the morning. Imagine taking a deep breath, savoring its warmth and comfort."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture yourself wrapped in your favorite sweater. Feel its softness and warmth surrounding you like a gentle hug."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall the feeling of a gentle rain on your face. Imagine standing in it, feeling refreshed and alive."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine walking through a field of tall grass. Feel the softness brushing against your skin as you breathe in the earthy scent."
        </item>
        <item>
"Think of the best sleep you've ever had. Picture yourself drifting off, wrapped in peace and complete relaxation."
        </item>
        <item>
"Remember the sound of birds singing in the morning. Imagine listening to them now, feeling peaceful and awake."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a loved one smiling at you. Feel the warmth and happiness of their love and the joy of being together."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine yourself sitting by a crackling fireplace. Feel its warmth and listen to the comforting sounds as you relax."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a favorite childhood game. Picture yourself playing it, feeling light, joyful, and full of wonder."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of a clear blue sky on a beautiful day. Imagine yourself looking up, feeling free and full of possibility."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember the joy of learning something new. Imagine the excitement and curiosity filling you as you explore."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture yourself in a library, surrounded by books. Feel the excitement of endless stories and knowledge at your fingertips."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine a gentle massage relaxing every part of your body. Let the comfort and peace wash over you completely."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of your favorite scent in the world. Picture yourself surrounded by it, feeling grounded and uplifted."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Recall the taste of a delicious dessert you loved. Imagine savoring each bite, feeling the joy of indulgence."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a quiet beach at sunrise. Feel the calm and the soft light as you stand there, breathing in peace."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Imagine the feeling of warm sunshine after a cold day. Let it melt away any tension, filling you with comfort."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember the joy of giving someone a heartfelt gift. Picture their smile, feeling the warmth of generosity."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of the soft purr of a content cat. Imagine petting it, feeling its warmth and your own calmness."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture yourself watching a soft snowfall. Feel the peace and purity of the snowflakes drifting down around you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a time you felt truly in the moment. Imagine being there again, feeling calm, clear, and present."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine taking a deep breath in a fresh forest. Smell the trees, feel the cool air, and let it energize you."
        </item>
        <item>
"Remember the first time you visited a place you loved. Imagine that excitement and wonder filling you up."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture a quiet, moonlit night. Feel the calm of the world resting under the gentle light of the moon."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of the sound of a loved one’s voice. Imagine hearing it again, feeling comforted and connected."
        </item>
        <item>
"Recall the feeling of grass under your bare feet. Imagine walking across it, feeling grounded and free."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine floating on calm water. Feel the gentle support, letting go of tension and worries."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a beautiful flower garden. Smell the blooms and let their vibrant colors fill you with joy."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember a time when someone expressed gratitude for you. Imagine hearing it again and feeling appreciated."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Think of a warm bath on a cool day. Imagine sinking in, feeling every bit of warmth and relaxation."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture the first sight of the ocean. Feel the vastness and beauty inspiring awe and freedom."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a delicious homemade meal. Imagine savoring each flavor and feeling the comfort of home."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine watching a sunrise over a quiet city. Feel the peaceful energy of a new day unfolding."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture a fresh snowfall untouched by footprints. Feel the calm and beauty of the pristine landscape."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of a time you watched fireworks. Imagine the colors lighting up the sky, filling you with wonder."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall the smell of fresh herbs. Imagine holding them, breathing in their earthy, refreshing scent."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine taking a nap under a shady tree. Feel the coolness, listening to the gentle rustle of leaves."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Remember a surprise that made you happy. Picture it again, feeling the excitement and joy of the moment."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Picture yourself walking through a quiet, misty forest. Feel the mystery and calm of nature surrounding you."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine a cozy blanket around you on a rainy day. Feel its warmth, hearing the gentle sound of rain."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Recall a day when you felt completely happy and content. Picture it, feeling that same joy again."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Think of the scent of vanilla. Imagine it filling the air around you, warm and comforting."
        </item>
        <item>
"Picture yourself sitting by a calm river. Feel the tranquility of the water flowing gently past."
        </item>
        <item>
"Imagine biting into a crisp apple. Taste its sweetness and feel its refreshing crunch."
        </item>
        <item>
  "Recall the softness of fresh sheets. Imagine lying on them, feeling comforted and at ease."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Think of a garden filled with butterflies. Imagine standing among them, feeling joy and lightness."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Picture yourself listening to a beautiful song that moves you. Let the music fill you with emotion."
        </item>
        <item>
 "Imagine the smell of a fresh pine tree in winter. Breathe it in, feeling refreshed and alive."
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>